{
    "id": "94ba231645e7440fbd72353eafa753cb",
    "title": "Has vs. Have vs. Had",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d75e73f53a854fc4a28917ce887ec0de",
            "title": "Has vs. Have vs. Had",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Rita …………………. a pet dog.",
                    "description": "Use has with singular subjects.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. a strange experience yesterday.",
                    "description": "Yesterday shows past time hence, we use had here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "has",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My neighbour …………………. a farmhouse.",
                    "description": "Use has with singular subjects.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………. no right to use my computer.",
                    "description": "Use have with you, we and they.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. so much work to do now.",
                    "description": "Use have with I.",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "has",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………. a daughter who lives in Canada.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What a pleasant surprise! I …………………. no idea you were coming today.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "had",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We …………………. a wonderful time when we went swimming on the weekend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "has",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………………….. a wonderful time whenever we go swimming.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "has",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The baby …………………. a slight fever.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rani …………………. got a fine collection of stamps. She is quite proud of it.",
                    "description": "Use has with singular subjects. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………………… no excuse for doing this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}